naturessleep.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy | Nature's Sleep

* * *

**Product Information:**  
For questions about our products or for more information on how to choose the perfect sleep system, one of our sleep experts will gladly assist you.

Call: 1-877-557-5337  
Email: [info@naturessleep.com](mailto:info@naturessleep.com).

* * *

**Warranty Information:**  
Please have your warranty information and sales receipt available when you call.

Call: 1-877-557-5337  
Email: [customerservice@naturessleep.com](mailto:customerservice@naturessleep.com).

* * *

**To make a warranty claim or check the status of a claim:**  
Please have your warranty information and sales receipt available when you call.

Call: 1-877-557-5337  
Email: [warrantyclaim@naturessleep.com](mailto:warrantyclaim@naturessleep.com)   
Include the following: 

• your full name  
• address  
• phone number  
• date of purchase  
• store where purchased  
• sales receipt invoice number  
• item purchased  
• brief description of your claim

* * *

**Retailer Information:**  
If you are a retailer interested in our many specialty sleep products, please speak with a leader from our Sales Department.

Call: 1-877-557-5337  
Email: [b2bmanager@naturessleep.com](mailto:b2bmanager@naturessleep.com).

* * *

* * *

**Blogger Relations:**  
For questions regarding our blog or blogger relations, please email  
[blog@naturessleep.com](mailto:blog@naturessleep.com).

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

**Collection of Information**   
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists. 

**Distribution of Information**   
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security**   
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. 

**Privacy Contact Information**   
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

By e-mail: [customerservice@naturessleep.com](mailto:customerservice@naturessleep.com).  
By Phone: 1-877-557-5337 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
